Okay, so let's look at the lips. First of all, oil in. Take our brush, I prefer that it sits all.
Okay, we will look at the chin. Okay, so first, let's go and look at this dark shape in the lip.
Take some purple, burn some of it, maybe a touch of the other one to indicate that.
I'm not going all the way to the edge. Just leaving that edge in the same.
Okay, touch lighter, alizarin, burn some of it, just in the corner.
That lip, just on the other side. That lip there, maybe some red.
Somewhere at the underside of the chin, the lip, yeah, alizarin red, alizarin burn some of it.
Right there, I'm going to pick out this reflected light.
So, just going to go in with some red, orange, oops.
In there, reflected light, that works. Doesn't, I can come back in again.
Okay, so that's the reflected light. Okay, then this underside of the lip,
there's a bit of reflected light in there.
Then take some red, maybe a touch of burn somber, full red.
Let's pick that out there. Then on this side, yeah, maybe some red green corner here.
Okay, there's a bit of light being caught on the lip.
Give me some red, touch them in the alizarin.
That will work, some red, burn some alizarin.
Rather than reaching for the white, I'm not going all the way to the edge.
Okay, we're going to reinstate that violet in the corner there.
We've got the swirling border, orange for orange and alizarin.
I'm going to take that down, a touch of green.
We don't need to, slightly darker.
Okay, maybe a bit of red on that edge of the lip there.
On that edge, still need to soften that edge a bit more.
Make that shape a bit thicker.
Okay, then you've got the oral commissure shape, more green.
I'm going to do this with the alizarin, alizarin green on this shape, darker.
Into that with the alizarin, too much.
Okay, now we can start to look around the mouth.
So we'll look at this side first.
So, a bit more green around this side here.
Make it a darker version of this.
Okay, just here, got this darker accent.
Okay, then we can pick out that edge of the lip.
So here, we're not as dark.
I'm going to use something for the underside of the lip there.
In the lip, just a bit more on the green side as that turns away.
Okay, so we need to just darken this shape in there a bit more.
More on the red side.
It's slightly warmer, slightly.
That light shape is probably just a bit more yellow.
I'm going to lighten that up a bit.
And we'll look at this side of the muzzle.
Okay, so that's something quite kind of yellowy.
There's some green in there, alizarin, too light.
Check that.
There's something around there.
Okay, then from the septum, I'm just going to make that slightly darker.
In here, I'm going to pick out the lights after.
I'm going to pick out the lights in there.
Okay, so I'm going to take this colour.
Pick out that highlight of that slightly darker accent here.
I'm going to pick out the shape.
Okay, then I've got this muzzle.
So let's go slightly darker.
It turns away a bit lighter.
More on the pink side of the mouth there.
And just around the nose here, it gets a bit lighter.
Okay, then looking at the underside of the lip.
Okay, so darker red, green.
It's a yellow, too dark.
I've got the overall tone in there.
I'm going to pick something out.
Going back, dark again.
A bit more red in there.
That bit of corner shadow, green.
Okay, just along the edge of the lip.
It's a bit warmer.
And out of this, I think a bit darker towards the edge of the lip,
that little accent.
Okay, I've got this accent on the other side of the lip there.
It's a greenish tint.
Okay, corner of the mouth.
A bit lighter.
So somewhere from the green side.
Highlight.
Okay, now look at the bottom lip.
It's a side plane.
Quite warm as it hits the shadow.
Yellow's edge.
Quite red.
Okay, just looking at the side plane.
And here it gets a bit lighter.
I'll pick out this highlight.
An orangey colour.
Right as that.
Tone that down even more.
Okay, that's the finish.